{
    "subject": "resource/Roswolsky's_Mistress",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "Roswolsky's Mistress is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9575127363204956,
            "question": "Is 'Roswolsky's Mistress' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8745622038841248,
            "question": "What genres might the film 'Roswolsky's Mistress' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8494242429733276,
            "question": "What type of media is 'Roswolsky's Mistress'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8245999217033386,
            "question": "Where could I find more information about the film 'Roswolsky's Mistress'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8095427751541138,
            "question": "Are there any other films with similar themes to 'Roswolsky's Mistress'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7547498941421509,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the plot of 'Roswolsky's Mistress'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7518624067306519,
            "question": "Who are some actors who might have starred in 'Roswolsky's Mistress'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7047459483146667,
            "question": "What is the significance of the title 'Roswolsky's Mistress'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4471891224384308,
            "question": "What are some critical reviews or audience opinions on 'Roswolsky's Mistress'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3410365879535675,
            "question": "What historical period does 'Roswolsky's Mistress' likely depict?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Roswolsky's Mistress is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7261_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some critical reviews or audience opinions on 'Roswolsky's Mistress'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7261_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of the title 'Roswolsky's Mistress'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7261_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some actors who might have starred in 'Roswolsky's Mistress'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7261_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7261_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7261_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7261_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7261_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7261_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7261_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7261_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7261_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7261_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7261_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation result:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to document `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7261/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt`, Roswolsky's Mistress is mentioned as a 1921 film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention \"Die Geliebte Roswolskys (1921, [lit. Roswolsky\u2019s Mistress),\" which refers to a film from 1921. This information supports the statement that \"Roswolsky's Mistress is a type of Film.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}